{
    "subject": "resource/A._B._Masilamani",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "1990-04-05",
    "human_readable": "The death date of A. B. Masilamani is April 5, 1990.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9724764227867126,
            "question": "Is April 5th, 1990 a significant date for A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9156133532524109,
            "question": "What is the date of A. B. Masilamani's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914059579372406,
            "question": "What is A. B. Masilamani's death date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8848592042922974,
            "question": "Who died on April 5th, 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8535478115081787,
            "question": "A. B. Masilamani's death date is in which month?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445445895195007,
            "question": "In what year did A. B. Masilamani die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8127273917198181,
            "question": "On which day of the month did A. B. Masilamani die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766435742378235,
            "question": "What month and year did A. B. Masilamani die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7177273035049438,
            "question": "April 5th, 1990, is associated with which individual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4871969521045685,
            "question": "When did A. B. Masilamani pass away?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The death date of A. B. Masilamani is April 5, 1990.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9268_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=April 5th, 1990, is associated with which individual?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9268_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and year did A. B. Masilamani die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9268_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On which day of the month did A. B. Masilamani die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9268_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9268_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your question in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the triple (\"The death date of A. B. Masilamani is April 5, 1990\") is indeed supported by the context information provided, specifically from the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9268/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt`."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context clearly states under the section for A. B. Masilamani that his \"Death Date\" is April 5, 1990, which directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}